ebitbux.com 2018-12-16

# ebitbux - Privacy Policy

### 3.CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Service. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties.

  * 3.1. LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION : You must promptly notify us if your user name or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that user name or password from your account and update our records accordingly. You are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the Site and for any activities or actions under your password. You are advised to disable any feature of your web browser that saves your password for future use. We will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with the above.
  * 3.2. PUBLIC INFORMATION : The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.
